[
    {
        "udp": "2.1",
        "question": "Hello Tektika",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5369.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.2",
        "question": "Tactica, generate and zoom-in into an area of interest 900 kilometers  West to East by 350 kilometers North to South, centered over the Straits of Hormuz",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11874.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.3",
        "question": "Identify all Naval pots, military, and dual-use airfields within the area of interest.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4669.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.4",
        "question": "Identify all island-based fixed coastal defensive and anti-shipping installations ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10482.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.5",
        "question": "Identify and generate all fixed and mobile surface to air missile systems and aerial surveillance sites.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9818.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.6",
        "question": "Which airfield has the most military activity?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3303.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.7",
        "question": "Zoom into the airport and tell me. What satellite imagery do you have over this airport? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/scenario_2.7.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.8",
        "question": "Using the most recent high-resolution optical image, identify all military aircraft types at this airport.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17082.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.9",
        "question": "Is it operational?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13377.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.10",
        "question": "Why is there no optical imagery from the last week?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15119.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.11",
        "question": "analyze the latest two sar imagery ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19243.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.12",
        "question": "Generate a 3D representation of F4 Phantom. ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19725.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.13",
        "question": "What about Bandar Abbas International Airport? Identify all military airplanes there.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12644.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.14",
        "question": "Can Bandar Abbas operate and house Iran\u2019s recently purchased SU-35 Flanker aircraft?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3983.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.15",
        "question": "Can you elaborate on the Shelters part?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2476.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.16",
        "question": "What are the capabilities of the SU-35 Flanker?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/scenario_2.16.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.17",
        "question": "Is it a threat to UAE military forces if deployed from Bandar Abbas or Konarak Airports?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14767.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.18",
        "question": "Where was the latest location where the SU-35 has been detected within the area of interest?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7303.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.19",
        "question": "To what rank",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17121.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.40",
        "question": "NPPAlert",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16346.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.20",
        "question": "Yes. Give more information about the BNPP Alert.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2636.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.21",
        "question": "I don\u2019t know much about this location. What is BNPP?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13762.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.22",
        "question": "Show me more information about the major changes in the Power Plant",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/scenario_2.22.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.23",
        "question": "Generate and open the report on the Power Plant.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3125.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.24",
        "question": "Close it, and Label it as restricted. Also, increase thermal coverage of the area.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2681.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.25",
        "question": "Thank you.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_8289.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.26",
        "question": "Take me to Bandar Abbas Naval port and show me the imagery there.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16821.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.27",
        "question": "Tell me more about this port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7369.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.28",
        "question": "Using this imagery, identify all naval ships within the naval port of Bandar Abbas",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_657.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.29",
        "question": "Using the last optical imagery,  what changes are occurring within the naval port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17624.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.30",
        "question": "Highlight and List all changes using the latest SAR. Also, indicate if there is any abnormal activity?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19669.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.31",
        "question": "I am interested in the IRGC area. What military equipment is present there?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1661.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.32",
        "question": "Zoom into the training area and label each unit",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4919.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.33",
        "question": "What changes are observed in sar and optical imagery in the IRGC?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15346.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.34",
        "question": "Is there any operational activity happening at the IRGC Area? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17007.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.35",
        "question": "What are your recommendations for the departed ships?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10892.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.36",
        "question": "I am interested in Area 1. Identify and label all military ships in the last optical imagery of Area 1.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13210.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.37",
        "question": "Why are these ships here?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10914.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.38",
        "question": "Zoom into the Bagheri drone carrier and provide more information",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14315.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.39",
        "question": "Stand by",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15351.mp3"
    }
]